[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas：所有这些的替代方法是异步函数。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: So an alternative to all of that are Asynchronous functions.
异步函数，%s立即返回。
Asynchronous function,s return immediately.
你叫它，它就会回来。
You call it, it comes right back.
几乎没有时间的流逝。
There's almost no passage of time.
而成功或失败将在未来以某种方式被决定
And success or failure will be determined somehow in the future
当异步函数返回时。
when the Asynchronous function returns.
目前还没有解决办法。
There is no solution yet.
解决方案可能会在晚些时候出现，但不是现在。
The solution might happen maybe later but not now.
所以我们喜欢在轮流系统中使用异步函数。
So we like to use Asynchronous functions in Turn systems.
回合由外部事件(如消息传递)启动，或者
A Turn is started by an external event, such as delivery of a message, or
异步请求、用户操作或时钟滴答的完成。
a completion of an asynchronous request, a user action, or the ticking of the clock.
调用与该事件关联的回调函数，并
That a callback function associated with that event is called and
它一直运行到完成。
it runs to completion.
它不需要担心种族，因为没有别的
It doesn't have to worry about races because nothing else
将得到运行，直到它完成。
will get to run until it's finished.
当它返回时，转弯结束。
When it returns, the turn ends.
所以不需要线程，没有比赛，没有死锁。
So there's no need for threads, no races, no deadlocks.
这是一个非常可靠，非常简单的编程模型。
It's a very reliable, very straightforward programming model.
我们称它为转弯是因为来自国际象棋的游戏。
We call it turns because of games that comes from chess.
在国际象棋中，轮到我的时候，我可以控制棋子。
That in chess when it's my turn, I get to control the piece.
你不能碰任何棋子，直到我完成，然后它交换。
You don't get to touch any pieces until my turn is done and then it exchanges.
我们正在对函数和事件做类似的事情。
We're doing a similar thing with functions and events.
但是当你使用转弯时，它要求你必须
But when you're using turns it requires that you have to
遵循铁的转弯法则，那就是你永远不能阻挡。
follow the iron Law of Turns which says you must Never block.
你永远不能等待。
You must Never wait.
你必须快点完成。
You must Finish fast.
如果您有任何不能的代码，则必须阻止或
If you have any code which can't, which has to block or
必须等待，否则不能很快完成。
has to wait or can't Finish quickly.
它必须被隔离并在单独的进程中运行。
It has to be isolated and run in a separate process.
不允许在转弯系统中运行。
It is not allowed to run in the Turn system.
所以这是一个成本权利。
So that's a cost right.
它的意思是，你可以运行一些代码，但是
It means, you're allowed to run some code but
有一些代码是绝对不允许你运行的。
there's some code which you're definitely not allowed to run.
我们通常在事件循环中执行此操作。
We usually do this in an Event Loop.
事件循环是基于TURN的系统。
Event loops are Turn based systems.
而且他们都有利弊。
And they come with Pros and Cons.
Pro是一个巨大的Pro。
The Pro is a huge Pro.
它完全没有种族和死锁。
It is Completely free of races and deadlocks.
这是一个巨大的优势。
And that's a huge advantage.
任何应用程序都不应该被编写的系统。
Any system that applications should never be written.
我认为在使用线程的系统中，因为它只是
I think in systems that use threads because it's just
太难推理了，也太不可靠了。
too hard to reason about them and it's too unreliable.
另一个专业是只有一个堆栈和
Another Pro is that there is Only one stack and
我们每次转弯都重复使用那个堆栈。
we reuse that stack on every Turn.
所以它的内存效率非常高，这根本不值得关注。
So it's extremely memory efficient which is of no interest at all.
再说一遍，因为内存太便宜了。
Again, because memory is so cheap.
事实上，我们的记忆效率是无关紧要的。
The fact that we're memory efficient is irrelevant.
更重要的是，它的开销非常低。
What's more important is that it is Very low overhead.
因为我们在事件循环中所做的就是从事件队列中删除一些内容，
Because all we're doing in the Event Loop is take something off an Event queue,
把它交给一个函数，让它运行，接受下一个，依此类推。
hand it to a function, let it run take the next one so on.
所以开销很小。
So there's very little overhead.
而在线程系统中，您需要进行大量的锁定，
Whereas in a threaded system, you're doing lots of locking,
您正在进行大量的流程切换和上下文切换。
you're doing lots of process switching, and context switching.
哪些是CPU上最贵的东西知道怎么做。
Which are the most expensive things at CPU know how to do.
在一个以术语为基础的系统中，你不是这样做的，你只是在做一些事情
In a term base system, you're not doing that you're just pull something off
队列并运行它，拉它并运行它。
the queue and running it, pulling it and running it.
它也是一个令人惊讶的弹性编程模型。
It's also a surprisingly Resilient programming model.
如果一个回合失败，通常情况下程序仍然可以继续。
If a Turn fails, it's usually the case that the program can still go on.
例如，如果您使用任何Web浏览器
For example, if you ever take any web browser and
打开调试器，直接进入Web。
open up the debugger and just go wading out into the Web.
你会看到几乎一连串的失败。
You're gonna see for almost a constant string of failures.
令人惊讶的是，网页中总是有多少失败。
It's amazing how much failure is going on in web pages all the time.
但是如果没有打开调试器，就看不到它。
But if you don't have a debugger open, you don't see it.
现在，在线程环境中，
Now, in a threaded environment when one of those,
当某件事失败时，将会有一个异常出现在
when something fails, then there'll be an exception in one of
其中一个线程中的库存将会受到伤害，它将尝试恢复。
the stocks in one of the threads will get on wound and it'll try to recover.
但与之相比，该线程现在可能处于不一致的状态
But that thread may now be in an inconsistent state compared
其他线程，因为它失去了所有的上下文。
to the other threads because it's lost all of this context.
因此，这可能导致级联线程故障。
And so, that could lead to cascading thread failures.
因此，它往往是一个相当脆弱的模型。
And so, it tends to be a fairly brittle model.
然而，我们在Web浏览器中看到的是，只要仍有任何按钮
Whereas, what we see in web browsers is as long as there is any button that still
工作，用户可以找到它。
works and the user can find it.
他们很有可能完成交易
There's a good chance they're going to be able to complete the transaction and
从来不知道这件事在幕后发生了巨大的失败。
never know that the thing has been failing hugely behind the scenes.
现在，这里有一些重要的缺点。
Now, there's some important cons here.
最重要的缺点是程序决不能阻止必须完成的提交循环
The most important con is that Programs must never block commit turns must finish
很快，我们必须遵守转弯法则，这绝对是一个骗局，但是
quickly that we have to obey the law of turns, that is definitely a con but
这是必须要尊重的事情。
it's something that has to be respected.
另外，另一个缺点是程序是由内而外编写的
Also, another con is that Programs are written inside out and
这会让一些人哭泣。
that makes some people cry.
他们称之为，这是控制的反转。
They call it, it's inversion of control.
这是不自然的，这是一种不切实际的方式
It's unnatural, it's an unrealistic way to
写一些我们做不到的程序太难了[听起来]。
write programs which we can't do it's too hard and [SOUND].
但事实上，这并不难。
But actually it turns out it's not hard.
其实很简单。
It's actually pretty easy.
所以我们在事件驱动的系统中做事情，它们是基于的，
So we do things in Event driven systems, they're Turned based,
没有先发制人，这真的很好，使他们非常可靠。
there's No pre-emption which is really good that makes them very reliable.
我们将事件与行动联系起来。
We associate Events with actions.
事实证明，尽管人们抱怨内心很难
And it turns out, despite the people who are complaining that it's very hard inside
既不自然又不自然。
out and unnatural.
它实际上非常容易，而且实际上初学者可以做到。
It's actually very Easy and in fact beginners can do it.
其实很难。
It's actually very hard.
事实上，即使在具有以下功能的系统上，所有用户界面也是如何实现的
And in fact, it's how all user interfaces are implemented even on systems that have
穿线。
threading.
因为事实证明这是实现用户界面的最佳方式。
Because it just turns out this is the best way to implement a User interface.
线程具有事件循环和
Threading has Event loops and
异步编程有很长的历史。
Asynchronous programming has a long history.
它是在实时系统、实验系统和游戏系统中完成的
It was done in real time systems, in experimental systems and game systems for
很长一段时间。
a long time.
直到Macintosh它才进入主流。
It doesn't get into the mainstream until the Macintosh.
Macintosh是第一款消费设备，尽管它的价格有点昂贵
Macintosh is the first consumer device although it's kind of expensive for
消费设备。
a consumer device.
其仅以基于回合的方式可编程。
Which is programmable only in a Turn based manner.
在此之前
Prior to that,
一切都在使用阻塞IO，一直回到4chan。
everything has been using blocking IO going all the way back to 4chan.
我们对此的记忆是，当苹果推出时，
And our memory of this is that when Apple introduced, and
史蒂夫·乔布斯于1984年推出了Macintosh。
Steve Jobs introduced the Macintosh in 1984.
它改变了世界，而且
It changed the world, and
使苹果成为世界上最成功的公司之一。
turned Apple into one of the world's most successful companies.
事实并非如此。
And that's not actually what happened.
这台机器几乎使苹果破产。
This machine came very close to bankrupting Apple.
部分原因是他们不能卖出很多，原因是
And part of the reason was that they couldn't sell very many and the reason for
那就是他们不能说服程序员为
that was that they couldn't convince programmers to write programs for
这台机器。
this machine.
因为他们以前从未见过事件循环
Because they'd never seen an Event Loop before and
不知道如何在那个模型中写程序。
didn't understand how to write programs in that model.
他们抱怨这不自然，太难了，从里到外，[声音]，
And they were complaining it's unnatural, it's too hard, it's inside out, [SOUND],
我们不会这么做的。
we're not gonna do it.
相反，他们为MS DOS写作。
Instead, they wrote for MS DOS.
这是可怕的和糟糕的。
Which was horrible and crappy.
这是有史以来最糟糕的事情之一，它的销量比这个高出几个订单。
One of the worst things ever imagined which outsold this by several orders.
太荒谬了。
It was just ridiculous.
所以改变这一切的是，
So the thing that changed this,
使这台机器获得成功的是HyperCard。
which turned this machine into a success, was HyperCard.
HyperCard是由Bill Atkinson构建的系统。
HyperCard was a system that was built by Bill Atkinson.
比尔·阿特金森写道，QuickDraw，
Bill Atkinson had written, QuickDraw,
这是最初的Macintosh的图形层。
which was the graphics layer of the original Macintosh.
他还编写了第一个绘画程序，名为MacPaint。
He also wrote the first paint program called, MacPaint.
今天很难将它识别为绘画程序，因为它只有两种颜色
It's hard today to recognize it as a paint program because it only had two colors
黑白分明。
black and white.
但这是一个非常免费的机器
But it was a very it came free with a machine and
当你买了一台Macintosh电脑，这就是它的全部用途。
when you bought a Macintosh that was literally all there was to do with it.
所以，人们用那幅叫做艺术的画做了很多事情。
And so, people did a lot of stuff with that painting called it art.
他的下一个程序是HyperCard。
His next program was HyperCard.
他拍摄了MacPaint，并允许它同时处理几张图片，
He took MacPaint and allowed it to work on several pictures at the same time,
只有一个是可见的。
only one of which would be visible.
他把这些图片称为卡片，文件就是一叠卡片或一堆卡片。
He called these pictures cards and that a file was a stack of cards or a stack.
然后，他有了一个想法，他可以把按钮放在卡片上
And then, he got the idea that he could put buttons on the cards and
将这些按钮连接到行为并将字段放在这些卡上
wire those buttons to behavior and put fields on those cards and
允许这些字段包含文本。
allow those fields to contain text.
然后他可以搜索并处理。
Which he could then search for and process on.
然后，他添加了事件驱动编程
And then, he added an Event driven programming
语言到所谓的超语言。
language to that called HyperTalk.
这是一种事件驱动的编程语言。
Which was an Event driven programming language.
里面的一切都是事件，你会说，on key up，
Everything in it was events and you would say things like, on key up,
鼠标按下等，初学者喜欢HyperCard。
on mouse down and so on, and beginners loved HyperCard.
他们把所有的东西都放进了超级卡里。
They got all into a HyperCard.
他们在写东西。
They were writing stuff.
他们从非常简单的小事件处理程序开始
They'd start with very simple little Event handlers and
然后开始做一些更复杂的事情。
then start doing stuff that was much more sophisticated.
发明了全新的应用程序类别，所有这些应用程序都运行在HyperCard中。
Inventing whole new classes of applications that all ran into HyperCard.
有预测称HyperCard将成为未来的
There were predictions that HyperCard was going to be the future of
软件开发。
software development.
如果不是苹果把它撞到地上，它可能已经被毁了。
And it might have, had Apple not run it into the ground.
Atkinson最初要求Steve Jobs将其分发给
Atkinson originally demanded of Steve Jobs that it be distributed for
免费与Macintoshes。
free with Macintoshes.
乔布斯也同意了，这就是他们几年来的做法。
And Jobs agreed, and that's how they did it for several years.
一旦他们看到它是多么成功，
Once they saw how successful it was,
他们决定我们需要弄清楚如何将其货币化。
they decided we need to figure out how to monetize this.
在这样做的过程中，他们把它杀死了。
And in the process of doing that they killed it to death.
但它起作用了，它启发了浏览器中发生的事情。
But it worked and it inspired stuff that happened in the browser.
事实上，你可以看到COMPs概念中的家居用品
In fact, you see that home thing that the comps concept of
主页来自HyperCard
the home page came out of HyperCard